<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab_1</string>
    <string name="Recipes">Recipes</string>
    <string name="Language">EN</string>
    <string name="Breakfast">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="Lunch">Lunch</string>
    <string name="Dinner">Dinner</string>
    <string name="Back">Back</string>
    <string name="Rec_1">Semolina balls</string>
    <string name="Rec_2">Shakshuka</string>
    <string name="Rec_3">Apple fritters</string>
    <string name="Ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_1">1) Milk - 500 ml \n2) Semolina - 160 g \n3) Flour - 2 tbsp. spoons \n4) Egg - 1 pc. \n5) Vegetable oil - 40 ml \n6) Vanillin - 2 pinches \n7) Sugar - 60 g \n8) Salt - 1 pinch</string>
    <string name="Cooking">Cooking</string>
    <string name="Cooking_1">1) Boil milk in a saucepan \n2) Continuously stirring the milk with a whisk, add semolina in a thin stream. Cook the porridge for about 3 minutes until thickened. The porridge should be thick \n3) Place the finished porridge in a bowl and leave to cool until warm. \n4) Then beat the egg into the semolina porridge, add sugar, vanillin and a small pinch of salt \n5) Stir until smooth \n6) With your hands soaked in water, form the semolina dough into a thick round cake and roll it in flour \n7) Form the rest of the balls in this way \n8) Heat a frying pan with vegetable oil and place some of the semolina balls there \n9) Fry the meatballs over low heat for 3 minutes on each side until golden brown \n10) Fry all the meatballs this way \n11) Serve the meatballs hot, warm or cooled, with honey, jam or condensed milk</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_2">1) Eggs - 4 pcs \n2) Tomatoes - 5 pcs. \n3) Red bell pepper - 1/2 pcs. \n4) Fresh chili pepper - 1/2 pcs. \n5) Onions - 1 pc. \n6) Garlic - 3 cloves \n7) Sugar - 1 teaspoon \n8) Ground sweet paprika - 1 teaspoon  \n9) Black peppercorns - 6 pcs. \n10) White peppercorns - 5 pcs. \n11) Coriander, grains - 10 pcs. \n12) Dry basil - 1 teaspoon \n13) Parsley (finely chopped) - 1 teaspoon</string>
    <string name="Cooking_2">1) Finely chop the sweet pepper \n2) Chop the onion \n3) Finely chop the garlic \n4) Remove seeds from hot peppers and chop them too \n5) Cut the tomatoes with seeds \n6) Grind all the spices in a mortar: two types of pepper, coriander, basil and paprika \n7) Pour vegetable oil into a heated frying pan, fry the garlic and hot pepper for 2-3 minutes \n8) Add onion \n9) Add bell pepper and 1 teaspoon of sugar there \n10) Add tomatoes. Simmer over low heat for 8 minutes, add all the spices and salt \n11) Using a spoon, make a small depression in the stewed vegetables for each egg and pour the eggs into it  \n12) Continue frying the shakshuka over low heat for 5-6 minutes until cooked. The egg white should turn white, but the yolk should remain runny \n13) Before serving, sprinkle shakshuka with herbs. Serve in a frying pan</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_3">1) Apples - 3 pcs. \n2) Sugar - 2 tbsp. spoons \n3) Egg - 1 piece \n4) Flour - 4 tbsp. spoons \n5) Ground cinnamon - 0.5 teaspoon \n6) Garlic - 3 cloves \n7) Vegetable oil - for frying</string>
    <string name="Cooking_3">1) Peel the apples and cut out the cores. Grate the apples on a coarse grater \n2) Place the grated apples into a deep bowl. Add sugar \n3) Add cinnamon and egg to apples \n4) Stir the mass \n5) Then gradually add flour, mixing well with a spatula \n6) Place a tablespoon of apple dough into a well-heated frying pan with oil, forming small pancakes \n7) Fry apple pancakes over low heat for 3 minutes on each side \n8) Serve apple pancakes with honey or sour cream</string>
    <string name="Rec_4">Mackerel roll with prunes and cheese, baked in sour cream</string>
    <string name="Rec_5">Lagman with chicken</string>
    <string name="Rec_6">Pasta \'Carbonara\'</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_4">1) Fresh frozen mackerel - 1 pc. \n2) Sun-dried prunes without pits - 4-6 pcs. \n3) Hard cheese - 40 g \n4) Onions - 80 g (0.5-1 pcs.) \n5) Butter - 20 g \n6) Sour cream (10% fat) - 100 g \n7) Fresh parsley - a few sprigs \n8) Salt - to taste \n9) Ground white pepper - to taste \n10) Ground nutmeg - to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_4">1) Thaw the mackerel in advance. Preheat the oven to 180 degrees \n2) Fill the prunes with hot water and leave so that they become softer and more flexible \n3) Dry the prunes and cut into small pieces \n4) Cut the mackerel lengthwise, remove the entrails and backbone. We take out all the bones, cut off the tail and fins. We wash the fish layer and dry it with paper towels. \n5) Cover the mackerel layer from the inside with cling film and gently beat it with a culinary hammer so that it becomes flatter and more uniform on all sides. \n6) Salt and pepper the fish on all sides and leave under film \n7) Peel the onion and cut into small cubes. Grate the cheese on a fine grater. Chop the parsley. \n8) Fry the onion in butter for 5-7 minutes, until golden and soft. \n9) Transfer the onions to a baking dish. \n10) Place cheese and chopped prunes on the fish. \n11) Roll the mackerel into a tight roll. We pin the edges with toothpicks so that the roll holds its shape. Place the roll in the pan with the onions. \n12) Sprinkle the fish roll with nutmeg and pour over sour cream. Then sprinkle again with nutmeg, salt and pepper. Place the pan in an oven preheated to 180 degrees for 20-25 minutes. \n13) Mackerel roll with prunes and cheese is ready. \n14) Sprinkle the finished dish with fresh parsley and serve.</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_5">1) Noodles - 60 g. \n2) Chicken fillet - 300 g. \n3) Tomatoes - 2 pcs. \n4) Bell pepper - 1 pc. \n5) Carrots - 2 pcs. \n6) Onions - 1-2 pcs. \n7) Tomato paste - 2 tbsp. spoons \n8) Sugar - 1 tbsp. spoon \n9) Salt - 3 pinches \n10) Ground black pepper - 3 pinches \n11) Vegetable oil - 40 ml</string>
    <string name="Cooking_5">1) Rinse the chicken fillet, dry it, remove films and veins. \n2) Cut the chicken fillet into medium pieces. Pour vegetable oil into a cauldron or frying pan with high sides and heat it. Add chicken fillet there and fry for about 7-10 minutes until golden brown. \n3) Peel the carrots and onions, wash and cut into cubes. Add to the chicken and fry for another 5-7 minutes until the vegetables are soft. \n4) Wash the tomatoes and bell peppers, remove the seeds from the peppers. Cut the vegetables into medium cubes and add to the pan with the chicken. Add sugar and 2 pinches of salt. Stir and simmer the chicken fillet with vegetables for about 15 minutes over medium heat. \n5) Meanwhile, boil water in a saucepan, add a pinch of salt and boil the noodles until tender, about 7-10 minutes. Then drain the noodles in a colander and return them to the pan. \n6) Add tomato paste and ground black pepper to the chicken and vegetables. Pour in 0.5 cups of water, mix everything carefully. Simmer for exactly 5 minutes. (If desired, you can add washed and chopped herbs.) \n7) Place boiled noodles in deep plates and top with gravy with chicken and vegetables. Garnish the chicken lagman with herbs and serve immediately!</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_6">1) Spaghetti - 400 g. \n2) Boiled-smoked brisket - 200 g. \n3) Chicken egg - 1 pc. \n4) Yolks - 3 pcs. \n5) Parmesan cheese - 75 g. \n6) Butter - 2 tablespoons \n7) Olive oil - 1 tbsp. \n8) Garlic - 2 cloves \n9) Salt - to taste \n10) Black pepper - to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_6">1) Cut the brisket into small cubes. \n2) Heat a frying pan, melt 1 tbsp. spoon of butter and place the brisket there. Add 2 cloves of garlic, previously crushed with a knife. Fry the brisket over low heat for 10 minutes, the fat should render out of it, but it should remain soft. After frying, remove the garlic. \n3) Add 1 tbsp to boiling water. spoon of salt, 1 tbsp. a spoonful of olive oil and spaghetti. Cook the spaghetti as directed on the package; it is important to follow the indicated cooking time in order to cook the spaghetti correctly. \n4) Separate the whites from the yolks of three eggs. Place 3 yolks and one egg with white into a bowl, add salt and pepper (1 pinch each), beat well and add 2 tbsp. spoons of grated cheese. Mix. \n5) Place the finished spaghetti in a colander, leaving 1.5 cups of the water in which they were cooked. \n6) Turn off the heat under the frying pan with the brisket, add the spaghetti, add 1 tbsp. spoon of butter and pour in the beaten eggs and cheese. \n7) Mix everything thoroughly, gradually add 1 glass of spaghetti water and 2 tbsp. spoons of cheese, stirring constantly so that the eggs do not curdle. \n8) Distribute the spaghetti among plates, add the brisket on top, sprinkle with ground black pepper and grated cheese. Carbonara pasta is ready.</string>
    <string name="Rec_7">Julienne with chicken and mushrooms</string>
    <string name="Rec_8">Jambalaya</string>
    <string name="Rec_9">Casserole \'Melt in your mouth tenderness\'</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_7">1) Chicken fillet - 400 g. \n2) Champignon mushrooms - 300 g. \n3) Onions - 100 g. \n4) Cream 20-30% - 200 ml. \n5) Hard cheese - 150 g. \n6) Vegetable oil - 2 tbsp. spoons \n7) Salt - to taste \n8) Ground black pepper - to taste \n9) Salt - to taste \n10) Greens (basil or lettuce) - for decoration</string>
    <string name="Cooking_7">1) Cut the chicken fillet into small pieces. \n2) Fry the chicken in vegetable oil for a few minutes until half cooked. Finely chop the onion, add to the chicken and fry the chicken fillet with onions for another 3-4 minutes. \n3) Coarsely chop the champignons and add to the pan. After the moisture from the mushrooms has evaporated, add salt and pepper and cook the chicken with onions and mushrooms for another 5-7 minutes, until golden brown. \n4) Pour cream over the meat and mushrooms, warm everything together a little. \n5) Grate the cheese on a coarse grater and place on top. Turn off the heat and cover the pan with a lid. \n6) When the cheese has melted after 3-5 minutes, the julienne with mushrooms and chicken can be served. \n7) If your frying pan allows it, garnish the chicken julienne with basil leaves and serve directly in this dish.</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_8">1) Sausages (preferably smoked or smoked) - 400 g. \n2) Rice - 350 g. \n3) Onions - 1 pc. \n4) Bell pepper - 200 g. \n5) Tomatoes - 300 g. \n6) Garlic - 2 cloves \n7) Tomato paste - 1 tbsp. spoon \n8) Vegetable oil - 60 ml \n9) Fresh parsley - 1 bunch \n10) Salt - to taste \n11) Ground black pepper - to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_8">1) Make cross-shaped cuts on the tomatoes. Pour boiling water over the tomatoes and set aside while we work on other vegetables. \n2) Cut the peeled onion into small cubes. Finely chop the peeled garlic with a knife. \n3) Remove the stems and seeds from the sweet bell pepper and cut into small pieces. \n4) Peel the tomatoes and cut them into cubes. \n5) Peel the sausages from the packaging film and cut into circles. \n6) Fry the sausages in vegetable oil. Let\'s set it aside for now. \n7) In the container in which we will cook the jambalaya (a deep frying pan or saucepan will do), heat the vegetable oil. Fry the onion until transparent. \n8) Add sweet pepper to the onion and lightly fry. \n9) Add tomatoes, garlic and tomato paste. Salt and pepper. \n10) Add sausages and rice there. Stir and add hot water. The water should be about 1.5-2 cm higher than the contents of the frying pan or saucepan. Reduce the heat, cover with a lid and simmer until the rice is ready. \n11) Sprinkle the finished dish with chopped parsley.</string>
    <string name="Ingredients_9">1) Raw potatoes, peeled - approximately 800 g. \n2) Minced meat - 600 g. \n3) Onions (small) - 2-3 pcs. \n4) Tomatoes - 2 pcs. \n5) Bell pepper - 1 pc. \n6) Hard cheese - 100 g. \n7) Chicken egg - 1 pc. \n8) Milk (optional) - for mashed potatoes \n9) Butter - 10 g. \n10) Vegetable oil - for frying \n11) Salt - to taste \n12) Pepper - to taste \n13) Greens - to taste \n14) Seasoning for minced meat - to taste</string>
    <string name="Cooking_9">1) First of all, boil the potatoes. Don\'t forget to salt the water well. Cook the potatoes until tender, 20-25 minutes. \n2) Cut onions, peppers and tomatoes into small pieces. \n3) In a well-heated frying pan with vegetable oil, fry the onion, bell pepper and minced meat. Add tomatoes, salt, pepper and your favorite seasonings for minced meat to the fried minced meat with vegetables. Leave to simmer for another 5-10 minutes until the minced meat is completely cooked. \n4) Make mashed potatoes with butter and egg from boiled potatoes. If necessary, add a little hot milk. Season the finished mashed potatoes with salt to taste. \n5) Grate the hard cheese. \n6) Form a casserole. To do this, first pour half of the mashed potatoes into the pan and carefully smooth it out. Next, distribute the fried minced meat with vegetables, also leveling. \n7) Spread the remaining half of the mashed potatoes evenly on top. Cover everything with grated cheese. \n8) Place potato casserole with minced meat and cheese in a preheated oven until the cheese melts. This is approximately 10-15 minutes. Sprinkle the finished potato-meat casserole with herbs, cut into portions and serve!</string>
    <string name="choose_your_language">Choose your language</string>
    <string name="Russian">Русский</string>
    <string name="English">English</string>
    <string name="Japanese">日本語</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="Cooking_porridge">Cooking porridge</string>
    <string name="Fry_the_meatballs">Fry the meatballs</string>
    <string name="Fry_garlic_and_pepper">Fry garlic and pepper</string>
    <string name="Lets_stew">Let\'s stew</string>
    <string name="Continue_frying_until_done">Continue frying until done</string>
    <string name="Frying_pancakes">Frying pancakes</string>
    <string name="Fry_the_onion">Fry the onion</string>
    <string name="Oven_timer">Oven timer</string>
    <string name="Fry_the_fillet_until_golden_brown">Fry the fillet until golden brown</string>
    <string name="Add_vegetables_and_fry_further">Add vegetables and fry further</string>
    <string name="Stir_and_simmer">Stir and simmer</string>
    <string name="Cooking_noodles">Cooking noodles</string>
    <string name="Lets_simmer_everything_together">Let\'s simmer everything together</string>
    <string name="Frying_the_brisket">Frying the brisket</string>
    <string name="Fry_fillet_with_onions">Fry fillet with onions</string>
    <string name="Fry_after_adding_mushrooms">Fry after adding mushrooms</string>
    <string name="Cooking_potatoes">Cooking potatoes</string>
    <string name="Stew_vegetables_with_potatoes">Stew vegetables with potatoes</string>
    <string name="Ready">Ready</string>
</resources>